Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2012
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky and flutist Bettina Danielle Berger of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_094)
- Composer Fred Lerdahl in a masterclass with student composers Colin Labadie, Juan V. Colon Hernandez, and Tyler Capp at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_095)
- Student composer Nissim Schaul with violoncellist Christophe Mathias, violinist Veronique Mathieu, and percussionist Michael Compitello of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal of Schaul's work Trio at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_096)
- Harpist Kristen Moss Theriault and flutist Bettina Danielle Berger of Ensemble Interface performing student composer Nathan Kelly's work Harbor Music at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_097)
- Conductor Scott Voyles with student composer Jonghee Kang in a rehearsal of Kang's work Drawing at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_098)
- Percussionist Michael Compitello of Ensemble Interface in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_099)
- Conductor Scott Voyles with percussionist Michael Compitello in a rehearsal with Ensemble Interface at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_100)
- Conductor Scott Voyles with percussionist Michael Compitello, flutist Bettina Danielle Berger, and violoncellist Christophe Mathias in a rehearsal with Ensemble Interface at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_101)
- Violoncellist Christophe Mathias of Ensemble Interface with a student composer Onur Yildirim in a rehearsal for Yildirim's work Mus-I zaman at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_102)
- Conductor Scott Voyles directing Ensemble Interface in a performance of student composer Onur Yildirim's work Mus-I zaman at June in Buffalo 2012. Performers left to right: violinist Veronique Mathieu, violist Anne Lanzilotti, violoncellist Christophe Mathias, clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky, percussionist Michael Compitello, flutist Bettina Danielle Berger, and harpist Kristen Moss Theriault., 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_103)
- Conductor Scott Voyles with Ensemble Interface after a performance of student composer Onur Yildirim's work Mus-I zaman at June in Buffalo 2012. Performers left to right: pianist Anna D'Errico, violinist Veronique Mathieu, violist Anne Lanzilotti, violoncellist Christophe Mathias, clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky, percussionist Michael Compitello, flutist Bettina Danielle Berger, and harpist Kristen Moss Theriault., 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_104)
- Conductor Scott Voyles with Ensemble Interface after a performance of student composer Onur Yildirim's work Mus-I zaman at June in Buffalo 2012. Performers left to right: pianist Anna D'Errico, violinist Veronique Mathieu, violist Anne Lanzilotti, violoncellist Christophe Mathias, clarinetist Yevgeny Dokshansky, percussionist Michael Compitello, flutist Bettina Danielle Berger, and harpist Kristen Moss Theriault., 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_105)
- Clarinetist Jean Kopperud playing a tube instrument built for the performance of composer David Felder's work Rare Air: Blews at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_106)
- Clarinetist Jean Kopperud performing composer David Felder's work Rare Air at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_107)
- Conductor James Baker directing a performance by the New York New Music Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2012. Performers left to right: pianist Stephen Gosling, violinist Curtis Macomber, violoncellist Chris Finckel, clarinetist Jean Kopperud, and flutist Jayn Rosenfeld, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_108)
- Guitarist Jeff McLeod, saxophonist Steve Baczkowski, and trombonist Jonathan Lombardo of the Genkin Philharmonic performing at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-07, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_109)
- Saxophonist Steve Baczkowski, trombonist Jonathan Lombardo, and drummer Matthew Felski of the Genkin Philharmonic performing at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-08, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_110)
- Saxophonist Steve Baczkowski, guitarist Jeff McLeod, trombonist Jonathan Lombardo, and drummer Matthew Felski of the Genkin Philharmonic performing at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-08, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_111)
- Trombonist Jonathan Lombardo, violinist Lazara Nelson, percussionist Tom Kolor, and trumpet player Jon Nelson of the Genkin Philharmonic performing at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-08, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_112)
- Composer Yeung-Ping Chen with violinist Yuki Numata in a rehearsal of Chen's work Light and Tear at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_113)
- Student composer Andres Carrizo with guitarist Zane Merritt and percussionist Tom Kolor in a rehearsal of Carrizo's work We Guide the Birth of Waves at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_114)
- Brad Lubman, conductor of Signal, at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_115)
- Members of Signal in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_116)
- Student composer Eun Young Lee with pianist Steven Beck in a rehearsal of Lee's work Mool at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_117)
- Conductor Brad Lubman directing Signal in a performance of composer Julia Wolfe's work Impatience at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_118)
- Conductor Brad Lubman directing Signal in a performance of composer Julia Wolfe's work Impatience at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_119)
- Conductor Brad Lubman with Signal after a performance of composer Julia Wolfe's work Impatience at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_120)
- Conductor Brad Lubman with Signal after a performance of composer Julia Wolfe's work Impatience at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_121)
- Composers Fred Lerdahl, Steven Stucky, and Robert Beaser at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_122)
- Conductor Brad Lubman directs Signal in a performance of Louis Andriessen's work La Passione with vocalist Jamie Jordan and violinist Courtney Orlando at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_123)
- Conductor Brad Lubman directs Signal in a performance of Louis Andriessen's work La Passione with vocalist Jamie Jordan and violinist Courtney Orlando at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_124)
- Conductor Brad Lubman directs Signal in a performance of Louis Andriessen's work La Passione with vocalist Jamie Jordan and violinist Courtney Orlando at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_125)
- Conductor Brad Lubman with Signal, vocalist Jamie Jordan, and violinist Courtney Orlando after a performance of Louis Andriessen's work La Passione at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-09, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_126)
- Composers Robert Beaser and David Felder introducing a performance of Beaser's Guitar Concerto by guitarist Elliot Fisk and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-10, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_127)
- Guitarist Elliot Fisk performing Robert Beaser's Guitar Concerto with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-10, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_128)
- Guitarist Elliot Fisk performing Robert Beaser's Guitar Concerto with JoAnn Falletta conducting the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-10, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_129)
- Guitarist Elliot Fisk with conductor JoAnn Falletta after a performance of Robert Beaser's Guitar Concerto with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-10, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_130)
- Composer Robert Beaser and Guitarist Elliot Fisk after a performance of Beaser's Guitar Concerto with conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-10, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_131)
- Composer Robert Beaser and Guitarist Elliot Fisk after a performance of Beaser's Guitar Concerto with conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2012, 2012-06-10, 1 digital image (tiff format) (Image-file jib2012_132)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
June in Buffalo (Festival) (Buffalo, N.Y.)--Photographs; Composers--Photographs; Music festivals--New York (State)--Buffalo--Photographs; Musicians--Photographs
Genres
Digital photographs; Portrait photographs
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2000
Mus. Arc. 18
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2000 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2001
Mus. Arc. 19
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2001 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2002
Mus. Arc. 20
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2002 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2003
Mus. Arc. 21
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2003 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2004
Mus. Arc. 25
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2004 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2005
Mus. Arc. 27
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2005 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2006
Mus. Arc. 29
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2006 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2007
Mus. Arc. 38
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2007 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2008
Mus. Arc. 39
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2008 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2009
Mus. Arc. 50
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2009 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2010
Mus. Arc. 55
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2010 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2011
Mus. Arc. 56
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2011 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2013
Mus. Arc. 66
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2013 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2014
Mus. Arc. 67
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2014 June in Buffalo.
June in Buffalo Photograph Collection
A selection of images from the June in Buffalo festivals are available through University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.